You're on the sofa burning up Your fever's at
99.8 You're lost inside a waking dream A
prisoner of her hate Your system's crashed,
your mind is full Of ghosts you can't erase
You're shaking, scared and far away In this cold
and empty space So we put the disc inside the
tray, dwelled our fantasy. We dimmed the lights
and pressed the play. A wall of sound, our new
decree. It's swirling around you on the floor, a
fortress made of friends. This is the night your
mother swore officially in love A sister's love
is on the screen A cheesy, epic, eddy sound We are
the fortress, we're the shield We're all gay The
love around will be the heroes in your plot The
love the tyrant never got will burn a shadow from
your mind The family he will never find
Your exit's clean, you're safe for girls A puppy
pile of care We're here to fight the fever We're
breathing your same air We'll bring you soup and
ginger ale We'll hold you till you're strong
This is the place where you belong Where you
belong We are the fortress.
We'll be the heroes in your plot. The love the
tyrant never got. We'll burn a shadow from your
mind. The family here will never die.
Your records swing, your cyphers curl Drown out
the bound industrial beat Let the 80s guitars
roar And signal his defeat The Sinclair
protocols are dead This is your new code instead
Sisters, love is on the screen A cheesy, epic,
80s sound We are the fortress, wear the shield
We'll be the heroes in your blood The love the
tyrant never got We'll burn a shadow from your
mind The family here will never old
We'll see you through
Mmmmmmmmmmmmm